Guide to the Ithaca pamphlet collection, 1863-1915.
Ithaca pamphlet collection
- "Report (No. 76) of the committee on medical societies and colleges, on petition of physicians of Tompkins county", Feb. 15, 1844; 7; no. 37
- "Report (No. 146) of the select committee on sundry resolutions of citizens of Orange county, and also sundry petitions from Orange, Tompkins, Columbia and Tioga counties, relative to a reform of the common school system", Mar. 20, 1846; 7; no. 38
- "Report (No. 62) of the committee on the erection and division of towns and counties, relative to a petition of the inhabitants of the counties of Chemung, Steuben, Yates and Tompkins, for the erection of a new county", Feb. 17, 1847; 7; no. 39
- "Report (No. 81) of the minority of the committee on towns and counties on the petitions relative to the erection of a new county from parts of Chemung, Steuben, Tompkins and Yates", Feb. 25, 1847; 7; no. 40
- Year-ending expenses and earnings for the Cayuga and Susquehanna Railroad, 1853; 7; no. 41
- "Report (No. 35) of the committee, relative to draining the Cayuga Marshes", Feb. 17, 1853; 7; no. 42
- "Report (No. 47) of the Commissioners of the Land Office in Relation to the Sale of Lands Donated to the State by the United States", Jul. 24, 1867; 7; no. 43